A Guide to the Governor Mark R. Warner, Press Office records, 2001-2006 (bulk 2002-2006)
Library of Virginia
- Series III. Photographs, 2001-2005 (Accession 42460).
  - Subseries A. Digital images on compact discs, 2001-2005 (Accession 42460).
    - Democratic Caucus, 2003 Feb. 21 (Box 62, Disc 4)
    - Press conference, 2003 Feb. 21 (Box 62, Disc 4)
    - DUI bill signing, 2003 Mar. 17 (Box 62, Disc 4)
    - National Governors Association winter meeting, 2003 Feb. 22-25 (Box 62, Disc 5)
    - Money Mailer announcement, 2003 Feb. 26 (Box 62, Disc 6)
    - Philip Morris, 2003 Mar. 4 (Box 62, Disc 7)
    - Susan Sweckers, 2003 Mar. 4 (Box 62, Disc 7)
    - Bill signing, 2003 Mar. 19 (Box 62, Disc 7)
    - McDuff, 2003 Mar. 24 (Box 62, Disc 7)
    - Jim Haywood, 2003 Mar. 25 (Box 62, Disc 7)
    - Portraits of Bill Leighty, 2003 Mar. 17 (Box 62, Disc 8)
    - Springfield Interchange bill signing, 2003 Mar. 18 (Box 62, Disc 9)
    - NASCAR event, 2003 Mar. 19 (Box 62, Disc 10)
    - Virginia Workforce Training, 2003 Mar. 26-27 (Box 62, Disc 10)
    - Fort Lee visit, 2003 Mar. 20 (Box 62, Disc 11)
    - Henrico Hospital bill signing, 2003 Mar. 26 (Box 62, Disc 11)
    - Capitol visits, 2003 Mar. 26 (Box 62, Disc 12)
    - State employees, 2003 Mar. 28 (Box 62, Disc 12)
    - PASS schools, 2003 Mar. 28 (Box 62, Disc 12)
    - Mansion Foundation dinner, 2003 Mar. 27 (Box 62, Disc 13)
    - Route 17 groundbreaking, 2003 Mar. 27 (Box 62, Disc 14)
    - Congressional Delegation, 2003 Mar. 31 (Box 62, Disc 14)
    - Bill signings (afternoon), 2003 Apr. 1 (Box 62, Disc 15)
    - Virginia Rural Association, Williamsburg, 2003 Apr. 1 (Box 62, Disc 15)
    - Highland Springs, 2003 Apr. 2 (Box 62, Disc 15)
    - Support our Troops proclamation, 2003 Apr. 2 (Box 62, Disc 15)
    - Dinner, 2003 Apr. 3 (Box 62, Disc 15)
    - VEA at Richmond Convention Center, 2003 Apr. 4 (Box 62, Disc 15)
    - Veterans, Bill Leighty, 2003 Apr. 7 (Box 62, Disc 15)
    - Bill signings and Support our Troops proclamation, 2003 Apr. 2 (Box 62, Disc 16)
    - Dinner, 2003 Apr. 3 (Box 62, Disc 16)
    - Arbor Day, 2003 Apr. 11 (Box 62, Disc 16)
    - Denise Goode, 2003 Apr. 14 (Box 62, Disc 16)
    - Governor Hunt, 2003 Apr. 14 (Box 62, Disc 16)
    - Social Security, 2003 Apr. 14 (Box 62, Disc 16)
    - Supreme Court dinner, 2003 Apr. 14 (Box 62, Disc 17)
    - Bill signings and Capitol renovations, 2003 Apr. 16 (Box 62, Disc 17)
    - Shadplanking, 2003 Apr. 16 (Box 62, Disc 17)
    - PASS event, Fairfield, 2003 Apr. 24 (Box 62, Disc 17)
    - Steps and shadplanking, 2003 Apr. 16 (Box 62, Disc 18)
    - Governor's Mansion, 2003 Apr. 22 (Box 62, Disc 18)
    - PASS schools, 2003 Apr. 24 (Box 62, Disc 19)
    - Holocaust Museum ribbon cutting, 2003 Apr. 28 (Box 62, Disc 20)
    - SOC appointments, 2003 Apr. 28 (Box 62, Disc 20)
    - HB 2445 bill signing, 2003 Apr. 30 (Box 62, Disc 20)
    - HB 2445 bill signing, 2003 Apr. 30 (Box 62, Disc 21)
    - Bill signing, 2003 May 2 (Box 62, Disc 22)
    - Bill signing, 2003 May 2 (Box 62, Disc 23)
    - Bill signing, 2003 May 2 (Box 62, Disc 24)
    - Midlothian Parkway, 2003 May 2 (Box 62, Disc 24)
    - Agency head bill signing, 2003 May 5 (Box 62, Disc 24)
    - Midlothian Parkway, 2003 May 2 (Box 62, Disc 25)
    - Heroes in Healthcare reception, 2003 May 6 (Box 62, Disc 25)
    - State employees, 2003 May 7 (Box 62, Disc 25)
    - Midlothian Parkway, 2003 May 2 (Box 62, Disc 26)
    - Girls and Boys State, 2003 May 2 (Box 62, Disc 26)
    - Hunters for the Hungry, 2003 June 18 (Box 62, Disc 26)
    - Wolfin' Down Books, 2003 June 26 (Box 62, Disc 26)
    - Greater Richmond Pipes and Drums, 2003 May 5 (Box 62, Disc 27)
    - Reception for agency heads, 2003 May 5 (Box 62, Disc 28)
    - Correctional Officers' Week, 2003 May 5 (Box 62, Disc 29)
    - Reception and candlelight ceremony, 2003 May 5 (Box 62, Disc 29)
    - Photo op, 2003 May 6 (Box 62, Disc 29)
    - Senior center, 2003 May 12 (Box 62, Disc 29)
    - Heroes in Healthcare reception, 2003 May 6 (Box 62, Disc 30)
    - Bill Mezger, VEC, 2003 May 6 (Box 62, Disc 31)
    - Virginia Public Service Week Governor's Award Ceremony, 2003 May 7 (Box 62, Disc 32)
    - Radio visits, 2003 May 8 (Box 62, Disc 33)
    - PASS events, 2003 May 8 (Box 62, Disc 33)
    - PASS event, 2003 May 8 (Box 62, Disc 34)
    - Bill signing, 2003 May 9 (Box 62, Disc 34)
    - PASS event, 2003 May 8 (Box 63, Disc 1)
    - Bill signing, 2003 May 9 (Box 63, Disc 1)
    - PASS event, 2003 May 8 (Box 63, Disc 2)
    - K-12, 2003 June 2 (Box 63, Disc 2)
    - Food Bank, 2003 June 5 (Box 63, Disc 2)
    - Literacy Foundation, 2003 June 23 (Box 63, Disc 2)
    - Project Graduation, 2003 July 11 (Box 63, Disc 2)
    - Bill signing, 2003 May 9 (Box 63, Disc 3)
    - Bill signing, 2003 May 9 (Box 63, Disc 4)
    - Roanoke 1 and 2, 2003 May 12 (Box 63, Disc 5)
    - Roanoke and Staunton visits, 2003 May 12 (Box 63, Disc 6)
    - Roanoke and Staunton visits, 2003 May 12 (Box 63, Disc 7)
    - Staunton visit, 2003 May 12 (Box 63, Disc 8)
    - Agriculture Month farm tour, 2003 May 13 (Box 63, Disc 9)
    - Senior Center visit, 2003 May 13 (Box 63, Disc 9)
    - Jamison's farm, 2003 May 27 (Box 63, Disc 10)
    - Levey Live, 2003 May 27 (Box 63, Disc 10)
    - PASS and press announcement, 2003 May 28 (Box 63, Disc 10)
    - Visit of Governor Warner to Busch Maulburg, Germany, 2003 May 21 (Box 63, Disc 11)
    - Wine Awards and CEO of Outback, 2003 June 2 (Box 63, Disc 12)
    - Genesis Academy visit, 2003 June 2 (Box 63, Disc 13)
    - Bond sale, 2003 June 4 (Box 63, Disc 13)
    - Food bank and fire station, 2003 June 5 (Box 63, Disc 13)
    - BRAC at Waterside, 2003 June 6 (Box 63, Disc 14)
    - Naval Base, 2003 June 6 (Box 63, Disc 14)
    - DGS Virginia Biotech building dedication, 2003 June 9 (Box 63, Disc 14)
    - Visit to Parksley, VA, 2003 June 7 (Box 63, Disc 15)
    - Infineon Tech, 2003 June 11 (Box 63, Disc 16)
    - Jamestown 2007, 2003 June 11 (Box 63, Disc 16)
    - Staunton call, 2003 June 16 (Box 63, Disc 16)
    - Boys State and basketball game, 2003 June 18 (Box 63, Disc 16)
    - Literacy Foundation, 2003 June 23 (Box 63, Disc 16)
    - Bill signing, 2003 June 12 (Box 63, Disc 17)
    - Bill signing, 2003 June 25 (Box 63, Disc 17)
    - Ask Why event, 2003 June 30 (Box 63, Disc 18)
    - Bill signings, 2003 June 30 (Box 63, Disc 18)
    - Bill, Tech. plate, 2003 June 30 (Box 63, Disc 18)
    - Mark and family, 2003 July 1 (Box 63, Disc 18)
    - Bayview ribbon cutting, 2003 July 2 (Box 63, Disc 19)
    - VITA picnic, 2003 July 8 (Box 63, Disc 19)
    - Tax reform meeting, 2003 July 10 (Box 63, Disc 19)
    - Galax visit, 2003 July 9 (Box 63, Disc 20)
    - Rock climbing, 2003 July 9 (Box 63, Disc 21)
    - Virginia Citizenship Institute, 2003 July 10 (Box 63, Disc 21)
    - Project Graduation, 2003 July 11 (Box 63, Disc 22)
    - Governor's conference room, 2003 July 22 (Box 63, Disc 22)
    - Governor's Fellows, 2003 July 22 (Box 63, Disc 22)
    - Mission of Mercy volunteer event, 2003 July 25 (Box 63, Disc 22)
    - Disputanta, 2003 July 30 (Box 63, Disc 22)
    - Spend Management Initiatitves roll-out, 2003 July 23 (Box 63, Disc 23)
    - Self-help water project, 2003 July 24 (Box 63, Disc 23)
    - Spend Management Initiatives roll-out, 2003 July 24 (Box 63, Disc 24)
    - Self-help water project, 2003 July 24 (Box 63, Disc 24)
    - Mission of Mercy volunteer event, 2003 July 24 (Box 63, Disc 24)
    - Self-help water project, 2003 July 25 (Box 63, Disc 25)
    - Martinsville visit, 2003 July 31 (Box 63, Disc 26)
    - Martinsville visit, 2003 July 31 (Box 63, Disc 27)
    - Democrats reception, 2003 Aug. 12 (Box 63, Disc 27)
    - House in progress, 2003 Aug. 1 (Box 63, Disc 28)
    - Fort A.P. Hill, 2003 Aug. 12 (Box 63, Disc 28)
    - Martinsville and Halifax, 2003 Aug. 13 (Box 63, Disc 28)
    - Bias-based announcement, 2003 Aug. 20 (Box 63, Disc 28)
    - National Governors Association annual meeting, 2003 Aug. 16-19 (disc 1 of 2) (Box 63, Disc 29)
    - National Governors Association annual meeting, 2003 Aug. 16-19 (disc 2 of 2) (Box 63, Disc 30)
    - Lunch, Lottery, 2003 Aug. 20 (Box 63, Disc 31)
    - Organ donor, 2003 Aug. 21 (Box 63, Disc 31)
    - Tom and Thomas farewells, 2003 Aug. 21 (Box 63, Disc 31)
    - Dog photo op, 2003 Aug. 22 (Box 63, Disc 31)
    - Demo State Central, 2003 Aug. 23 (Box 63, Disc 31)
    - GAB building, 2003 Aug. 25 (Box 63, Disc 31)
    - DUI Taskforce, 2003 Aug. 27 (Box 63, Disc 32)
    - DUI Taskforce, 2003 Aug. 27 (Box 63, Disc 33)
    - Education for a Lifetime, 2003 Sept. 3 (Box 63, Disc 34)
    - Albert G. Horton Memorial Veterans Cemetery groundbreaking, 2003 Sept. 8 (Box 63, Disc 35)
    - Poquoson press conference, 2003 Sept. 20 (Box 63, Disc 36)
    - Hurricane Isabel damage at Claremont, 2003 Sept. 20 (Box 63, Disc 36)
    - Ghost Fleet after Hurricane Isabel, 2003 Sept. 20 (Box 63, Disc 36)
    - Poquoson tour, 2003 Sept. 20 (Box 64, Disc 1)
    - Tour of Richmond, 2003 Sept, 22 (Box 64, Disc 2)
    - Red Cross, 2003 Sept. 23 (Box 64, Disc 2)
    - Massey and Claremont, 2003 Sept. 24 (Box 64, Disc 2)
    - Sunken Meadows, Claremont and Smithfield, 2003 Sept. 24 (Box 64, Disc 2)
    - Church, Surry County, 2003 Sept. 27 (Box 64, Disc 2)
    - High speed ral, 2003 Sept. 29 (Box 64, Disc 2)
    - Senior Year Initiative, 2003 Oct. 1 (Box 64, Disc 3)
    - State Fair, 2003 Oct. 3 (Box 64, Disc 3)
    - Forbes CEO Summit reception, 2003 Oct. 3 (Box 64, Disc 4)
    - Hispanic reception, 2003 Oct. 7 (Box 64, Disc 5)
    - Israeli Ambassador, 2003 Oct. 7 (Box 64, Disc 5)
    - Israeli luncheon, 2003 Oct. 7 (Box 64, Disc 5)
    - Latino Advisory Board, 2003 Oct. 7 (Box 64, Disc 5)
    - Workforce Training, 2003 Oct. 7 (Box 64, Disc 5)
    - Education for a Lifetime, 2003 Oct. 8 (Box 64, Disc 5)
    - BRAC meeting, 2003 Oct. 10 (Box 64, Disc 5)
    - BRAC meeting, 2003 Oct. 10 (Box 64, Disc 6)
    - J. Sargeant Reynolds, 2003 Oct. 14 (Box 64, Disc 6)
    - Pre-K Initiative, 2003 Oct. 20 (Box 64, Disc 6)
    - World Access event, 2003 Nov. 6 (Box 64, Disc 7)
    - MasterBrand Cabinets, 2004 Jan. 15 (Box 64, Disc 8)
    - LEAP and other photo ops, 2004 Feb. 9-10 (Box 64, Disc 9)
    - Visit by Vice President of Congo, 2004 Feb. 10 (Box 64, Disc 10)
    - Battelle Memorial Institute, 2004 Feb. 11 (Box 64, Disc 10)
    - Model General Assembly, 2004 Feb. 11 (Box 64, Disc 10)
    - Virginia School Board Association, 2004 Feb. 18 (Box 64, Disc 11)
    - Delegate Bland, 2004 Feb. 18 (Box 64, Disc 11)
    - Loudoun High School group, 2004 Feb. 18 (Box 64, Disc 11)
    - Black political organization, 2004 Feb. 18 (Box 64, Disc 11)
    - Governor's friends, 2004 Feb. 18 (Box 64, Disc 11)
    - Virginia War Memorial, 2004 Feb. 18 (Box 64, Disc 12)
    - Virginia War Memorial news conference, 2004 Feb. 18 (Box 64, Disc 13)
    - National Governors Association winter meeting, 2004 Feb. 21-24 (Box 64, Disc 14)
    - Senator Potts visit, 2004 Feb. 25 (Box 64, Disc 15)
    - School leadership presenters at the Mansion, 2004 Mar. 8 (Box 64, Disc 16)
    - Governors High School summit, 2004 Mar. 8 (Box 64, Disc 17)
    - Press conference, 2004 Mar. 17 (Box 64, Disc 18)
    - Congressional Delegation group portrait, 2004 Mar. 29 (Box 64, Disc 19)
    - Trip to China, 2004 June 6-11 (Box 64, Disc 20)
    - National Governors Association conference, "salmon catching," 2004 July 18 (Box 64, Disc 21)
    - Dulles Corridor rail project grant announcement, 2004 July 22 (Box 64, Disc 22)
    - Photo op, 2004 Aug. 7 (Box 64, Disc 23)
    - Fiddler's Convention, 2004 Aug. 9 (Box 64, Disc 24)
    - Fiddler's Convention, 2004 Aug. 9 (Box 64, Disc 25)
    - Galax bike trip, 2004 Aug. 10 (Box 64, Disc 25)
    - Galax bike trip, 2004 Aug. 10 (Box 64, Disc 26)
    - NASCAR event, 2004 Sept. 11 (Box 64, Disc 27)
    - Southern Governors Association, 2004 Sept. 12 (Box 64, Disc 27)
    - Copies of all previously described images on Disc 27 (Box 64, Disc 28)
    - NASCAR event, 2004 Sept. 11 (Box 64, Disc 29)
    - Southern Governors Association, 2004 Sept. 12 (Box 64, Disc 29)
    - Southern Governors Association, 2004 Sept. 12 (Box 64, Disc 30)
    - Southern Governors Association, 2004 Sept. 12-13 (Box 64, Disc 31)
    - Microsoft Darden Curry announcement, 2004 Sept. 24 (Box 64, Disc 32)
    - Visit with bluegrass music legend Ralkph Stanley, 2004 Oct. 21 (Box 64, Disc 33)
    - Visit to Virginia National Guard at Petersburg, 2004 Dec. 20 (Box 64, Disc 34)
    - Colonial Williamsburg Foundation press conference, 2005 Jan. 6 (Box 64, Disc 35)
    - Higher Education reception, 2005 Feb. 11 (Box 64, Disc 36)
    - Huguenot High School visit, 2005 Mar. 16 (Box 64, Disc 37)
    - Visits to Japan and India, 2005 Apr. 18-28 (Box 64, Disc 38)
    - Government Performance Project appreciation reception, 2005 June 3 (Box 64, Disc 39)
    - Department of Health, CHAMPIONS, 2005 June 3 (Box 64, Disc 40)
    - Memo signing between Virginia and Kent of the United Kingdom, 2005 June 3 (Box 64, Disc 41)
    - American Bar Association proclamation signing, 2005 June 3 (Box 64, Disc 42)
    - Governor's Cup, 205 June 13 (Box 64, Disc 43)
    - Portraits of Heather Glissman and John Pezzeli, 2005 June 14 (Box 64, Disc 44)
    - Rail bill signing, 2005 June 17 (Box 64, Disc 45)
    - Virginia Beach boardwalk, 2005 June 17 (Box 64, Disc 45)
    - Baseball game, 2005 June 26 (Box 64, Disc 46)
    - National Governors Association annual meeting, 2005 July 16 (disc 1 of 3) (Box 64, Disc 47)
    - National Governors Association annual meeting, 2005 July 16 (disc 2 of 3) (Box 64, Disc 48)
    - National Governors Association annual meeting, 2005 July 16 (disc 3 of 3) (Box 64, Disc 49)
    - Images of Hop Wells, Laura Moffitt, pharmacist, and Tim Bass, 2005 Aug. 5 (Box 64, Disc 50)
  - Subseries B. Event files, 2001-2005 (Accession 42460).
    The event files are arranged chronologically by the date of the event featured. The files may have matching compact discs in Subseries A, but some do not. Many of the files contain only contact sheets of photographs taken. In some cases actual photographs and/or negatives are included as well. When large photographs are present, or if the file contains related paperwork, they are housed in a folder. If small photographs are present, they are housed in paper envelopes to prevent loss or misplacement. Many of the event files also contain documents relating to particular events photographed. Often included is email correspondence containing the Governor's schedule, background information, whether the event was open to the public, and the length of time the Governor would be in attendance. Files include events such as legislators' receptions, bill signings, press conferences, visits from foreign dignitaries, and meetings with various individuals and groups. Many files contain information, photographs, and negatives from more than one event. Repetitive entries exist because pictures and other material for a particular event may be housed in more than one folder, or because several events shared a roll of film. In these cases, each event and its date are listed on the folder, as well as in the container listing of the finding aid. The files are arranged according to the earliest event date featured in each folder, and the events are listed in that order here.
    - Miscellaneous photographs, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Open house at the Governor's Mansion, 2002 Jan. 13 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Swearing-in ceremony for Cabinet members, 2002 Jan. 13 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - DGS reception, 2002 Jan. 17 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Legislators' reception, 2002 Jan. 17 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Swearing-in of Secretary of the Commonwealth Anita Rimler, 2002 Jan. 20 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Swearing-in of Secretary of the Commonwealth Anita Rimler, 2002 Jan. 20 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. mass meeting, 2002 Jan. 21 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. mass meeting, 2002 Jan. 21 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Budget presentation, 2002 Jan. 22 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Visit with Dickenson County officials, 2002 Jan. 24 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - First bill signing, 2002 Jan. 30 2002 Jan. 30 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Nurses' Association visit, 2002 Jan. 30 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Tazewell County legislative reception, 2002 Jan. 30 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Press conference, 2002 Jan. 30 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Press photos (AP) with the Governor, 2002 Jan. 30 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Fredericksburg Christian School kids, 2002 Jan. 30 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Bill signing, Executive Order 7, 2002 Jan. 31 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Meeting with Pulaski teachers, 2002 Feb. 4 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Attempt to get to Grundy, Appalachian School of Law, 2002 Feb. 4 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Meeting with Pulaski teachers, 2002, Feb. 4 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Leadership Blackstone Capitol visit, 2002 Feb. 5 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - NOVA senior citizens Capitol visit, 2002 Feb. 5 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - United Mine Workers meeting, 2002 Feb. 5 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Ministers' reception, 2002 Feb. 6 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Advisory Commission for Higher Education Board appointments, 2002 Feb. 7 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - WorldCom and MCI Employee Town Hall meeting, 2002 Feb. 8 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Times Community Papers Editorial Board meeting, 2002 Feb. 8 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - WorldCom and MCI Employee Town Hall meeting, 2002 Feb. 8 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Times Community Papers Editorial Board meeting, 2002 Feb. 8 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Thomas Jefferson High School visit, 2002 Feb. 11 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Thomas Jefferson High School visit, 2002 Feb. 11 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Race car #83 photo op, 2002 Feb. 11 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Virginia Public Safety Foundation Commonwealth Valor Awards, 2002 Feb. 11 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Thomas Jefferson High School visit, 2002 Feb. 11 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Public Safety Foundation Commonwealth Valor Awards, 2002 Feb. 11 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Public Safety Foundation Commonwealth Valor Awards, 2002 Feb. 11 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Virginia Association of Technology Student Associations, 2002 Feb. 12 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Virginia Association of Technology Student Associations, 2002 Feb. 12 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Virginia Association of Technology Student Associations, 2002 Feb. 12 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Virginia First Committee reception, 2002 Feb. 12 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Meeting with Grundy and Buchanan County officials, 2002 Feb. 13 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Meeting with Appalachian School of Law Projects Committee, 2002 Feb. 13 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Grundy visit, Appalachian School of Law, 2002 Feb. 13 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Bill signing, Chap Peterson and Mark Cole, 2002 Feb. 14 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Bill signing, Chap Peterson and Mark Cole, 2002 Feb. 14 (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - Virginia College Savings Plan press conference, 2002 Feb. 14 (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - Reception for docents at Governor's Mansion, 2002 Feb. 14 (Box 65, Folder 34)
    - Segway test ride, 2002 Feb. 15 (Box 65, Folder 35)
    - Capital One meeting of Commission on Efficiency and Effectiveness, 2002 Feb. 18 (Box 65, Folder 36)
    - Photos with Wanda Walton's daughter, 2002 Feb. 18 (Box 65, Folder 36)
    - Governor's Commission on Efficiency and Effectiveness meeting, 2002 Feb. 19 (Box 65, Folder 37)
    - Southampton High School exhange students, 2002 Feb. 19 (Box 65, Folder 38)
    - Exceptional Children's Week, 2002 Feb. 19 (Box 65, Folder 38)
    - Governor Dr. Orji Uzor Kalu of Nigeria visit, 2002 Feb. 19 (Box 65, Folder 39)
    - Legislators' reception, 2002 Feb. 20 (Box 65, Folder 40)
    - Pages' reception, 2002 Feb. 21 (1 of 2) (Box 65, Folder 41)
    - Pages' reception, 2002 Feb. 21 (2 of 2) (Box 65, Folder 42)
    - Elliot Sadler visit, 2002 Feb. 26 (Box 65, Folder 43)
    - Town of Woodstock officials' Capitol visit, 2002 Feb. 27 (Box 65, Folder 44)
    - Legislators' reception, 2002 Feb. 28 (Box 65, Folder 45)
    - iParent Magazine, 2002 Feb. 28 (Box 65, Folder 46)
    - Read Across America Day school visit, 2002 Mar. 1 (Box 65, Folder 47)
    - Outstanding Faculty Awards presentation, 2002 Mar. 1 (Box 65, Folder 48)
    - Coeburn Middle School Jr. Beta Club photo op, 2002 Mar. 1 (Box 65, Folder 49)
    - Model General Assembly, 2002 Mar. 1 (Box 65, Folder 50)
    - Chamberlayne Elementary School visit, 2002 Mar. 1 (Box 65, Folder 50)
    - Chaine reception, 2002 Mar. 2 (Box 65, Folder 51)
    - Naming of new Parole Board, 2002 Mar. 4 (Box 65, Folder 52)
    - Swearing-in of Secretary of Public Safety, 2002 Mar. 4 (Box 65, Folder 52)
    - Seven Hills Middle School visit, 2002 Mar. 6 (Box 65, Folder 53)
    - VHTP job fair, 2002 Mar. 6 (Box 65, Folder 54)
    - Basketball game, 2002 Mar. 6 (Box 65, Folder 55)
    - Great Bridge High School wrestling team visit, 2002 Mar. 7 (Box 65, Folder 56)
    - Great Bridge High School wrestling team visit, 2002 Mar. 7 (Box 65, Folder 57)
    - Bath County High School football team visit, 2002 Mar. 7 (Box 65, Folder 57)
    - Bath County High School football team visit, 2002 Mar. 7 (Box 65, Folder 58)
    - Alexis Barr's going-away party, 2002 Mar. 7 (Box 65, Folder 59)
    - Armed Services representatives' Capitol visit, 2002 Mar. 8 (Box 65, Folder 60)
    - Chicken's Snack Bar stop-by, 2002 Mar. 8 (Box 65, Folder 61)
    - Bill signings, 2002 Mar. 8 (Box 65, Folder 62)
    - Bill signing, HB 1336, 2002 Mar. 8 (Box 65, Folder 63)
    - Photos with Senator Howell, 2002 Mar. 8 (Box 65, Folder 63)
    - Chicken's Snack Bar stop-by, 2002 Mar. 8 (Box 65, Folder 64)
    - Photos with Senator Howell, 2002 Mar. 8 (Box 65, Folder 64)
    - VCU Health System Community Health Education Center dedication, 2002 Mar. 11 (Box 65, Folder 65)
    - Shenandoah Club with Roanoke business leaders, 2002 Mar. 12 (Box 65, Folder 65)
    - Danville/Pittsylvania Chamber of Commerce luncheon, 2002 Mar. 12 (Box 65, Folder 66)
    - Coordinated Economic Relief Center opening, 2002 Mar. 12 (Box 65, Folder 66)
    - Carilion groundbreaking, 2002 Mar. 12 (Box 65, Folder 67)
    - Barr Labs announcement, 2002 Mar. 12 (Box 65, Folder 67)
    - Roanoke business leaders dinner, 2002 Mar. 12 (Box 65, Folder 68)
    - Cocktail party at the Governor's Mansion, 2002 Mar. 13 (Box 65, Folder 68)
    - Cocktail party at the Governor's Mansion, 2002 Mar. 13 (Box 65, Folder 69)
    - Virginia Congressional Delegation meeting, 2002 Mar. 18 (Box 65, Folder 69)
    - Virginia Congressional Delegation meeting, 2002 Mar. 18 (Box 65, Folder 70)
    - WTOP "Ask the Governor" show, 2002 Mar. 19 (Box 65, Folder 71)
    - Virginia Agriculture Week farm tour, 2002 Mar. 19 (Box 65, Folder 71)
    - NASCAR/Virginia Colleges press conference, 2002 Mar. 19 (Box 65, Folder 72)
    - Virginia Agriculture Week event, Berryville, 2002 Mar. 19 (Box 65, Folder 73)
    - Mansion dinner and cocktails, 2002 Mar. 20 (Box 65, Folder 73)
    - American Cancer Society bus tour, 2002 Mar. 20 (Box 65, Folder 74)
    - Buddies of Petersburg visit, 2002 Mar. 20 (Box 65, Folder 74)
    - Consul of Japan visit, 2002 Mar. 20 (Box 65, Folder 75)
    - Mansion dinner, 2002 Mar. 20 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Uninsured Medical Catastrophe Fund proclamation, 2002 Apr. 2 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Meeting with Senator Warren Barry, 2002 Apr. 2 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Bill signing ceremony, 2002 Apr. 3 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Bill signing, EVMS, Norfolk, 2002 Apr. 3 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Hampton Roads Maritime Association annual banquet, 2002 Apr. 3 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Hampton Roads Maritime Association annual banquet, 2002 Apr. 3 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Child Abuse Prevention Month kick-off, 2002 Apr. 4 (Box 66, Folder 6)